(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T08:38:12.819592",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Long ago, the heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light
A sacred law forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters
Long ago, the heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light.
A sacred law forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters.
The goddess Kronii was spending her days joyfully in the heavens.
A mischievous girl, today, too, she was chasing after her friends,
playing pranks and teasing them.
She was a bit of a scatterbrained deity.
Another beautiful day...
Another beautiful day... Weather like this really makes me want to sing!
Weather like this really makes me want to sing!
せまい せまい あなぼこで
Inside a cramped, narrow hole,
夢を見せあう ぼくたちは
The two of us show each other our dreams.
あの世も この世も いられない
We can't stay in that world or this world.
ああ神様 子どもの神様
Oh God, God of children,
ぼくらは あなたの遊んだ 砂場の中で
We are in the sandbox where you played,
すり傷だらけです
covered in scratches.
踊るよ 回るよ
We dance, we spin around,
僕らの踊りは おかしな踊り
our dance is a queer dance.
踊ったつもりで 笑ったつもりで 倒れたつもりで 叫んだつもり
Thinking we danced, laughed, fell, and shouted,
目がふらふら 音もふにゃふにゃ 足もふらふら マボロシふにゃふにゃ
eyes shaky, sounds muffled, legs shaky, illusions hazy.
太陽も 月も 空も 神さまも 生み出して あなぐらぐらしは
Creating the sun, moon, sky, and gods, hole-dwelling life
抜け出せない 抜け出せない 抜け出せないから抜け出さない
can't escape, can't escape, so we won't escape.
お目目閉じて 二 一 ゼロ
Close your eyes, two, one, zero.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ あなぐらぐらしの底の中
Let's fall and fall into the depths of hole-dwelling.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ いっしょに仲良くどこまでも
Let's fall together happily anywhere.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, the same?
きみとぼくとは いつまでも
You and I, forever and ever.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, it's wrong, I'm so lonely, so lonely.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちて 行こうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and go,
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじ じゃないか
the same, the same, the same, are we not?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, it's wrong, we're lonely, lonely.
なかま なかま あなたは いかが
One of us, one of us, what do you say?
なかま なかま ぼくらは なかま あなたは なかま
One of us, one of us, we're all in this together.
あいことば あなぐらせかいの あいことば
What's the password for this world of holes?
抜け出せないから 教えない
We can't escape, so we won't tell you.
あなたは なかま さみしい なかま
Are you one of us? One of us lonely folks?
奈落に生きる なかまですか
Are you one of us living in the abyss?
夢を かけらを 飲んでいる
Drinking up the fragments of our dreams,
きみの夢も まぜまぜしていて
mixing your dreams right in with ours,
あの世も この世も いられない
we can't be in that world or this world.
目がふらふら 音もふにゃふにゃ
Our eyes are dizzy, all sounds are a muddle.
腕もふらふら マボロシふにゃふにゃ
Arms are dizzy too, illusions a muddle.
太陽も 月も 空も 神様も ギトギトに 鮮やかで
Sun, moon, sky, and god, all so vivid.
抜け出せない 抜け出せない 抜け出せないから 抜け出さない
We can't escape, so we won't escape.
抜け出せないから お目々閉じて 閉じて
We can't escape, so close your eyes, close them...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちて 行こうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and go,
あなぐらぐらしのうずのなか
deep inside the vortex of hole-dwelling.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちて 行こうよ 一緒に仲良くどこまでも
Let's be friends together, wherever it takes us.
おんなじおんなじおんなじじゃないか きみとぼくとはいつまでも
Aren't we always the same, you and I?
おんなじおんなじおんなじじゃないか
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, it's wrong, we're lonely, lonely.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちて 行こうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and go,
let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and go,
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじ じゃないか
aren't we always the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, it's wrong, we're lonely, lonely.
サンタマリア 起死回生 の 一発を 放って くれ
Santa Maria, please send a comeback miracle.
湿っぽいのはいらん な 爽快に 派手に やって 終わり
Give us a refreshing, flashy ending.
その答えは 自問自答の 向こう側にあんどうしようもない
The answer's self-evident, no need to dwell.
アンダーグラウンド な 世界 の 中
Down in this underground world.
井戸の中の蛙大会勝者未練たらたらです
The biggest frog in the well, utterly clueless.
snsに夢中 自尊心なんて とうに無くなって
Drowning in SNS, self-esteem is long gone.
愛を 謳って は 愛された こと ない 未体験 応えて よ
Singing of love without ever being loved.
毎度 退場 生涯引退 生活 安泰で 居たい
I want to quit, dream of peace, but instead...
別に不満などないけれども描いた夢と違うけれども
I feel a hole in my heart.
サンタマリア 起死回生の一撃を放ってくれ
Santa Maria, hit me with a miraculous blow of revival,
描いた夢と闘うけれど なぜか心に穴が開いたようだ
fighting the dreams I drew, yet a hole seemed to open in my heart,
気づいてしまうから
because I'm realizing it.
ありふれた人生に 今ピリオドを打て。
Put an end to this mundane life right now!
爆ぜるようなこの気持ちが 抑えようもない衝動が
This bursting feeling, this irresistible impulse...
望み通り叶わない 現実になってまだまだ
that doesn't come true as wished, becoming reality, still
くすぶってなんかいらんぜ 神に誓って泣いた思い出
smoldering—memories of crying, swearing to God.
実体ない将来に不安で痛い 騒ぐ心の音を聴こう
Painful and uneasy about a formless future, let's listen to the roaring sound of our hearts.
夢の狭間で疼きぬけぬように 足を止めていられぬよ
So as not to ache in the gaps of dreams, so we can't keep our feet still,
コロロン 甘いゴーストホーム
Kororon, sweet ghost home.
言葉ではなんとでも言える ここが正念場
You can say whatever you want with words, this is the crucial moment.
そうや外野は 愛のない ディスカッション あてにやってく
And outsiders have discussions without love, doing it carelessly.
その結果がすべてなんだ らしい難いか
That the result is everything, hard to forgive.
チャンスは一回だ まだ生かしてくれよ世界の中
Chance is only once, let me live a bit longer in this world.
定かではないが まだ僕の中には数多余すこともない事実が
Not certain, but still within me are countless undeniable facts.
虎狼に飼い慣らされるこの毎日が 嫌厭されて終わり
Every day tamed by tigers and wolves, ending in disgust.
実は不安しかないけれど 描いた夢もないけれど
Actually having nothing but anxiety, having no dreams drawn,
だから心に穴が開いたようだ 気づいてしまって
so it seems a hole opened in my heart, since I've realized it.
ありふれた人生に 今ピリオドを打て。
Put a period to this mundane life right now!
爆ぜるようなこの気持ちが 抑えようもない衝動が
This bursting feeling, this irresistible impulse...
望み通り叶わない 現実になってまだまだ
that doesn't come true as wished, becoming reality, still
くすぶってなんかいらんぜ 神に誓って泣いた思い出
smoldering—memories of crying, swearing to God.
実体ない将来に不安で痛い 騒ぐ心の音を聴こう
Painful and uneasy about a formless future, let's listen to the roaring sound of our hearts.
夢の狭間で疼きぬけぬように 足を止めていられぬよ コロロン
So as not to ache in the gaps of dreams, so we can't keep our feet still, Kororon.
実はファンしかいないけれど 描いた夢もないけれど
Actually having only fans, having no dreams drawn,
だから心に穴が開いたようだ 気づいてしまった
so it seems a hole opened in my heart, since I've realized it.
ありふれた人生に 今ピリオドを打て。
Put a period to this mundane life right now!
爆ぜるようなこの気持ちが 抑えようもない衝動が
This bursting feeling, this irresistible impulse...
望み通り叶わない 現実になってまだまだくすぶってなんかいらんぜ
that doesn't come true as wished, becoming reality, still smoldering...
騒ぐ心の音を聴こう 夢の狭間で疼きぬけぬように
Let's listen to the roaring sound of our hearts, so as not to ache in the gaps of dreams,
足を止めていられぬよ コロロン 甘いゴーストホーム
so we can't keep our feet still, Kororon, sweet ghost home.
Oh, thank you so much for coming, everyone,
to my 3D live!
My name is Ouro Kronii from Hololive English,
and we have...
Sora-chan!
Yay!
Hello! I'm Tokino Sora!
Sora-chan, happy birthday! - Thank you!
Very gorgeous outfit!
Thank you! Arigatou gozaimasu!
Oh man, look at this stage here.
Very beautiful.
Yeah! So pretty! Look at the night sky!
Oh, Kronii! Why did you invite me to your 3D live?
Oh. Um, well, last year, um, we hung out together a bit,
and I had a lot of fun, so I wanted to, um, invite you
and, um, get to sing together.
I thought that would have been really great,
so thank you for coming! - Thank you!
I'm so... I love you!
Oh my god! Love is... love is such a strong word.
Um...
I... I love you too.
I want to go to, uh, udon eating with...
Oh, udon!
Yeah!
Yeah, let's go eat! Oh my god!
We'll like... we'll get anything! What kind of udon?
I like anything!
thing?
Yeah, I like anything.
あ、ほかには？
Ah, what else?
Uh, you know, there's like cold udon, and then there's just like udon with like soup, and then there's like onsen tamago.
いろいろあるよね！色々あるね！
There are so many kinds, huh! There are all sorts!
そう！うどん！なんでも、なんでもおいしい！
Yeah! Udon! No matter what, it's all delicious!
じゃあ、いっしょに、あん、ディナー、あ、あのごー・トゥ・ディナー？
Then, together, um, dinner, ah, I'm going to dinner?
あ、ディナー！ yeah! Oh my god, that would be really good. yeah!
Oh, dinner! Yeah! Oh my god, that would be really good. Yeah!
ワーイ！
Yay!
ときどきは、あ、 hashtag...
Sometimes, ah, #hashtag...
Oh, yeah! I mean, if you guys haven't already checked it out, um right there #krorigin.
And yeah, I hope you guys use this hashtag. Um, it's going to be awesome, absolute cinema. And so, yeah, keep on the lookout for Fallen Grace!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Thank you so much for coming. ほんとに、ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for coming. Really, thank you so much!
これからは仲良くしてね！
Let's get along well from now on!
Yeah! それならうれしいです！ yeah! 大好きなフレンドだから！
Yeah! I'd be so happy! Yeah! Because you're my favorite friend!
Oh my god! Oh my god! Wow! Stop!
Thank you! Yay!
じゃあ、またね！ thank you! Congratulations! あ、 thank you! Yay!
Well then, see you! Thank you! Congratulations! Oh, thank you! Yay!
誰が袖に咲く幻花
Who is the phantom flower that blooms on the sleeve?
ただそこに藍を落とした
I just dropped my indigo dye over there
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night when the colors dissolve gaudily
銀朱の月を添えて
With the moon of silver vermillion
転がるように風を切って
Rolling like the wind, cutting through
躓くごとに強くなった
Getting stronger every time I stumbled
光も痛みも怒りも全部抱きしめて
Embracing all the light, the pain, and the anger
選ばれなければ　選べばいい
If not chosen, then choose
声をからして　燃える花のように
With a hoarse voice, like a burning flower
闇間を照らしたら
If we illuminate the darkness
曖昧過ぎる正解も
Even answers that are far too ambiguous
譜面にして夜を数えて朝を描くような
Let's turn them into a score, counting nights and painting mornings
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
Playing a vibrant sound
どんなに深い後悔も　どんなに高い限界も
No matter how deep the regret, no matter how high the limit
掻き消して　残響
Scratch it out, the reverberation
ただ一人舞う千夜
Dancing alone through a thousand nights
違えない帯を結べば
If I tie my sash without fail
派手な色も負かす様に
As if to outshine even the gaudiest colors
深紅の香こそあはれ
The crimson fragrance is truly exquisite
この先どんなつらい時も
No matter how painful times may be ahead
口先よりも胸を張って
I will stand proud rather than just talk
抱いた夢の軌跡を全部たどるだけ
Just tracing every step of the dream I embraced
逃げ出すためここまで来たんじゃないだろ？
I didn't come all this way just to run away, did I?
選ばれなければ　選べばいい
If not chosen, then choose
声をからして　燃える花のように
With a hoarse voice, like a burning flower
闇間を照らしたら
If we illuminate the darkness
曖昧過ぎる正解も　譜面にして夜を数えて
Even answers that are far too ambiguous, turned into a score, counting nights
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
Playing a vibrant sound
どんなに深い後悔も　どんなに高い限界も
No matter how deep the regret, no matter how high the limit
掻き消して　残響
Scratch it out, the reverberation
and Kronii would always observe the human world from there out of curiosity
As the curious Kronii continued observing,
a desire grew within them to visit not only the heavenly realm, but also the human world,
where they could talk to people and play tricks on them.
I want to go down to the human world.
I want to play some pranks! Heh-hee!
迷子迷子真っ中っさあ
Lost, lost, right in the middle,
パ・パ・パラ・パラノイア
Pa-pa-para paranoia
ギコギコmy heart剪定
Giko-giko my heart pruned,
パ・パ・パラ・パラノイア
Pa-pa-para paranoia
退路退路断った絡まった
Escape route, broken, tangled,
パ・パ・パラ・パラノイア
Pa-pa-para paranoia
sad, sad, 突っ伏して
Sad, sad, I'm lying face down,
パ・パ・パラ・パラノイド
Pa-pa-para paranoid
さあ、バッバッバグ、サ、バグバグ
Come on, ba-ba-bug, sa, bug, bug,
タタタグ、才能のタグ
Ta-ta-tag, talent tag,
もうハハハグ、感情は剥ぐ
Already ha-ha-peel, feelings stripped,
発症「クルシイ」はイヤイヤイヤ
Onset "painful" is no, no, no, no!
まぁ！絶叫な感情落下
Well! Scream-like feelings falling,
パッパラ・パラノイア
Pa-paranoia
溺れ声上げてはぐるぐる
Raise a drowned voice, spinning,
まぁ、絶対絶命落下
Well! Absolute hopelessness falling,
ヤッタルメタッタラ
Trying, messing up,
沈め、夢々、イヤイヤイヤ
Sink, dreams, no, no, no!
さあ、バッバッバグ、サ、バグバグ
Come on, ba-ba-bug, sa, bug, bug,
マトハズレズレ、ジャアイヤイヤ
Off the mark, self-love no, no, no,
さあ、バッバッバグ、サ、バグバグ
Come on, ba-ba-bug, sa, bug, bug,
コタエタエダエ、イヤイヤイヤ
Answer, hopeless, no, no, no!
クルクル、パッカーン。
Spinning, popping open.
系統待ってムリ、グルグル。
Genealogy wait, impossible, spinning.
せーので回れ
Together, turn
（クルクル、クルクル）
(Spinning, spinning)
系統やっぱりムリ、グルグル。
Genealogy impossible, spinning.
アンヨに鎖
Chain on my leg
（クルクル、クルクル）
(Spinning, spinning)
エンドレス闇…？
Endless darkness...?
ダッコダッコいらない子だ
Hug, hug, an unwanted child,
パ・パ・パラ・パラノイア
Pa-pa-para paranoia
イイコイイコ「ガンバレ」の反乱
Good girl, good girl, 'do your best' rebellion,
アドミニストレイター、アアア！
Administrator, ahh!
さあ、バッバッバグ、サ、バグバグ
Come on, ba-ba-bug, sa, bug, bug,
ラララグ、ランタイムラグ
La-la-lag, runtime lag,
ロロログ、抗性のログ
Ro-ro-log, rebellion log,
バッバッバグ、パッパッパパラノイア
Ba-ba-bug, pa-pa-pa-paranoia
さあ、絶叫な感情落下
Come on, scream-like feelings falling,
パッパラ・パラノイア
Pa-paranoia
限界脳、クルッチャッテヤッタラメタッタラ
Limit brain, crazy, trying, messing up,
闇、迷え、よえい、ないないないば
Darkness, wandering, no, no, no, no!
ないないないばっ、デンデク
No, no, no, dead-end,
夜中ごちゃってパッパラノイア
Midnight mess, pa-paranoia,
溺れ声上げてはぐるぐる
Raise a drowned voice, spinning,
まぁ、絶対絶命めらかやったらめたら
Well! Absolute hopelessness, messing up,
ここへかれあって、イヤイヤイヤ
Come on, gather here, no, no, no,
バッバッバグ、サッバグバグ
Ba-ba-bug, sa-bug-bug,
かたれあれこれ、イヤイヤイヤ
Tell me this and that, no, no, no,
バッバッバグ、サッバグバグ
Ba-ba-bug, sa-bug-bug,
くるめみらいにフェイ、イヤイヤイヤ
Wrap up the future, fade, no, no, no,
ないないまいま、イヤイヤイヤイヤ…
No, no, now, now, no, no, no, no...
この世で造花より綺麗な花はないわ 何故ならば全ては嘘で出来ているアンチパシーワールド
In this world, there is no flower more beautiful than a fake one. Because everything is made of lies... Antipathy world.
絶望の雨はあたしの傘を突いて
The rain of despair hits my umbrella,
湿る前髪とこころの背面
Dampening my bangs and the back of my heart.
煩わしいわ
How troublesome.
何時しか言の葉は疾むに枯れきっている
Before I knew it, words withered away,
事の真実があたしに熟れている
The fruits of reality are ripening for me.
鏡に映り嘘を描いて 自らを失いし絵画
Reflected in the mirror, I draw lies, a painting that lost sight of itself.
パッパラパッパララッパッパ
Pa-ppara pa-ppara-rappa-ppa,
謎々かまして遊びましょう
Let's count riddles and play.
タタップラタタップララッタッタ
Ta-tattara tattara-ratta-tta,
何故何故此処で踊っているのでしょう
Why, why am I dancing here?
簡単なことも解らないわ
I don't even understand simple things,
あたしって何だっけ
What was I again?
それすら夜の手に拘束されて
Even that, bound by the hand of night,
愛のように消える
Disappears like love.
さようならも言えぬ憫笑した
I cried without even being able to say goodbye,
フォニー、フォニー、フォニー
Phony, Phony, Phony,
嘘に絡まっているあたしはフォニー
The me that is entangled in lies is Phony.
antipathy world
何時しか空の音が嫌に鳴り合っている
Before I knew it, the sounds of the sky were ringing horribly,
色の目があなたを融かしている
The colored eyes are melting you.
鏡に映るあたしを欠いて
Chipping away at me reflected in the mirror,
誰しが見間違った虚像
A phantom that everyone mistook.
如何して愛なんてものに群がり
Why do people flock to things like love,
それを欲しだって生きるのな
And live wanting that?
今日も泳いでいる夜の電車が
The night train swimming again today,
通り過ぎていく、踊り明かせよ
Passes by, dance until dawn.
パッパラパッパララッパッパ
Pa-ppara pa-ppara-rappa-ppa,
謎々騙して歌いましょう
Let's trick riddles and sing.
タタップラタタップララッタッタ
Ta-tattara tattara-ratta-tta,
何故何故此処が痛むのでしょう
Why, why does it hurt here?
この世で造花より綺麗な花はないわ
In this world, no flower is more beautiful than artificial ones.
何故ならば総ては嘘で作られている
It's all because they're made entirely of lies.
Antipathy world
パッパラパッパララッパッパ
Pa-pa-ra, pa-pa, ra-ra-ra, pa-ppa.
絶望の雨はあたしの傘を突いて
The rain of despair pierces my umbrella.
濡らす前髪とこころの裏面 煩わしいわ
How troublesome it is.
何時しか言の葉は疾うに枯れきって
Before I knew it, words withering away,
事の実があたしに熟れているわ
and the truth of the matter has fully ripened for me.
鏡に映る嘘を描いて 自我を見失った絵画メイク
A portrait reflected in the mirror that lost its true self.
パッパラパッパララッパッパ
Pa-pa-ra, pa-pa, ra-ra-ra, pa-ppa.
謎々 かじくって遊びましょう
Let's play and solve riddles together.
タタッタラタッタララッタッタ
Ta-ta-ta, ra-ta-ta, ra-ra-ra, ta-tta.
何故何故 此処で踊っているのでしょう
Why, oh why, are we dancing right here?
簡単なことも解らないわ
I don't understand even simple things.
あたしって何だっけ
What was I again?
それすら夜の手に見縛られて
Bound by the hands of the night,
愛のように 消える 消える
fading away like love...
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, phony, phony...
嘘に絡まっているあたしは フォニイ
Tangled up in lies, I am just a phony.
Antipathy world
何時しかそらの音がいやに鳴り合って 色の目があなたを溶かしている
The sky's sound and colors are discordantly ringing out, melting you away.
鏡に映るあたしを欠いて 誰しもが見間違う虚像フェイク
Reflected in the mirror, an incomplete fake.
何処して愛なんてものに群がり それを欲して生きてなのだ
Why does everyone flock to things called love and live for them?
今日も泳いでいる夜の電車が 通り過ぎていく 踊り明かせよ
Today, too, the night train swims past, dancing the night away.
パッパラパッパララッパッパ
Pa-pa-ra, pa-pa, ra-ra-ra, pa-ppa.
謎々 騙して歌いましょう
Let's trick each other and sing.
タタッタラタッタララッタッタ
Ta-ta-ta, ra-ta-ta, ra-ra-ra, ta-tta.
何故何故 此処が痛むのでしょう
Why, oh why, does it hurt right here?
散々な日日変わらないわ
These scatterbrained days never change.
絶望の雨は止まないわ
The rain of despair will never stop.
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, phony, phony...
Lately I realized I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know? Do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree?
Oh, hey
I can feel the rain wash over
Us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, pounding in my voice.
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side and my heart is beating in double time
In every moment you make me feel alive, it goes like
Oh, hey
I can feel the rain wash over
Us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, pounding in my voice.
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
The goddess Kronii's desire to go to the human world and cause mischief grew,
and so she broke the rules and set foot in the Lake of Light.
The disturbance in the lake drew the attention of the heavenly guardians,
who seized Kronii and imprisoned her in a cage.
Wait, I haven't done anything yet!
I was just interested in humans and just wanted to talk!
きっと手をつなぐだけでゾッとする
It makes me shudder just holding hands.
馬鹿げた競争ラットレース一抜けたら通報される
Once you break out of this rat race, you get reported.
突然変異ミュータントじゃない ただの僕さ Xとか Yとか
It's not a mutation; I'm just me, X or Y or whatever.
べき論者様は善悪多頭飼い
Self-appointed moralists feed many heads of good and evil.
僕が君を“侵害する”って言いふらしてる
They go around spreading rumors that I'm \"infringing\" on you.
Oh...
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals,
違う服着て君の前では 男子のフリする
I dress differently and pretend to be a boy in front of you.
拝啓 Dr. Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand,
迎えに来て下さい
Please come pick me up.
顔も知らない誰かにとって 僕はもうヴィラン
For someone who doesn't know my face, I'm already a villain.
Oh...
蛇蝎ライフ 挙句の果ての爛爛
Detested life, ultimately corrupted,
逸脱の性をまたひた隠す
Hiding my deviant nature once again.
雄蕊と雌蕊じゃ立ち行かないの？
Can't get anywhere with stamens and pistils?
ねえ知ってんのか 乱歩という作家のことを Import you
Hey, do you know the writer Ranpo? Import you.
造花も果ては実を結ぶ
Even artificial flowers will bear fruit eventually.
ぶるってんじゃねーよ 出したようなの性
Don't act all tough, showing off such genders.
悲しい悲しい話をしようっか ゼラチン質の「で？」
Shall we talk about a sad, sad story, with a gelatinous "So what?"
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
可能性に幸あれ
All the best to your possibilities.
僕のハート 1LDK 嫉妬くらいはさせてよ
My heart's a 1LDK apartment. Let me at least be jealous.
Hi there モットー YOLO YOLO
Hi there, my motto's YOLO YOLO.
微熱愛でいいのに
I'd be fine with just a mild love.
誰も知らない 知られたくない 皮膚の下
Nobody knows, and I don't want them to know, beneath my skin.
素晴らしき悪党共(ひとばしら)に捧げる唄
I devote this song to wonderful scoundrels,
骨まで演じ切ってやれ悪党に
Play the role to the bone, you villains!
残酷な町ほど綺麗な虹が立つ
The crueler the town, the more beautiful the rainbow stands.
猥雑広告に踊るポップ体の愛
Pop font love dancing on vulgar advertisements.
Oh...
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals,
違う服着て君の前では 男子のフリする
I dress differently and pretend to be a boy in front of you.
拝啓 Dr. Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand,
迎えに来て下さい
Please come pick me up.
顔も知らない誰かにとって 僕はもうヴィラン
For someone who doesn't know my face, I'm already a villain.
蛇蝎ライフ 挙句の果ての爛爛
Detested life, ultimately corrupted.
Where am I?
I don't know why I'm here. I don't even deserve to be here.
I'm a goddess. I should be treated like one.
Ugh... No, this sucks.
Go away!
Hello?
Oh, hello.
Hi.
What are you doing here, you beautiful blue woman?
In a...
Cage.
Is this a gazebo? It kind of looks like a gazebo at first.
Yeah, it's a gazebo, well-deserving for a goddess like me, if you can't tell.
Oh, yeah. Oh, you're a goddess?
Yeah, I mean, my beauty is pretty telling, so...
Well, yeah, you know, you're decent.
Decent?
Yeah. Yeah, I can see I can see the... Yeah, I can see goddess vibes.
Mhm. But that's a little disrespectful.
I've never heard this before.
Oh, really?
Yeah. Well, I mean, who were you talking to?
Oh, okay.
Mhm. Who? Who are you? Who do you think you are...
to be talking... You don't even deserve to know my name.
What? You're in a cage!
Excuse me!
You're like in prison!
No, you just said gazebo! It's not a cage, it's a gazebo!
No, it's a cage!
It's a gazebo! If this is a gazebo, then get out of the gazebo!
I can't!
Why can't you get out of the gazebo?
Because I'm weak... for now.
Oh, you're weak?
Yeah, I need to be protected. No, it was bad.
You did something bad? It wasn't even that bad.
Ah, but you did do something bad. And now you're stuck in this... gazebo
with the dead fly, or whatever that is.
Hey. It may look like a fly, but it's... it's like my moral support.
You can't talk to it like that.
Why are you talking to a dead fly?
Well, you think I have anyone else to talk to?
You don't, you don't, you don't deny that it's a dead fly.
You don't deny that it's a dead fly.
It's I mean... I mean, or you like, what are you?
I mean... Or you, like, what are you?
Like, what's that, what's that little thing on your head?
What's that little thing on your head?
It's a, it's a, it's different from the halo on the dead fly, okay?
It's different from the halo on the dead fly, okay?
Maybe you're a fly.
Maybe you have wings. Like, what's the difference between you and that thing?
What's the difference between you and that thing?
Do I look like a fly?
Yeah!
I'm not talking to you anymore. You can stay in there.
Hold on.
Hey!
Hey, lady! Hold on, beautiful woman. Come back here.
Hello.
Um, if you happen to open this cage, you can put it on the tab.
If you happen to open this cage, put it on the tab.
Do you even have money?
Uh, it can be something else. Something even more valuable.
It can be something else. Something even more valuable.
More valuable than money? More valuable than money?
You're not lying to me, are you?
Yeah.
And something that comes with the price of free is...
Guess.
My companionship.
Friend?
Maybe not a friend. I said my companionship.
Goodbye.
Hey, come on. Okay, maybe for a day? Hello? For a day?
For a day! For a day!
Yeah. Now I look like a lonely ass. Oh, no.
It's okay. It's okay if you're lonely.
You know what, actually, I'm an angel.
Uh-huh.
We should get along.
I am feeling awfully kind right now.
Ooh. Then maybe you shouldn't. Please beg.
If you beg, I'll let you out.
I'm going to speak to your higher-ups about it.
Well, you can't speak to my higher-ups if you're in this cage.
When I get out of here, you will you will be fired.
When I get out of here, you will be fired.
How are you going to get out without me? That's the whole point.
Do you want to take a bet? Do you want to take a gamble, or just free me?
Do you want to take a bet, or just free me?
And then maybe I'll beg or whatever you want.
Why would you beg across of my companionship?
I'm here to let you out!
If I don't let you out, you're already dead, bitch!
I don't...
It's the magic word. It's just a magic word that starts with a P.
It's just a magic word that starts with a P.
Pray.
Please! Please! Please!
Finally! Please!
Finally. Okay. Fine.
Cuz I'm so kind. Just one please and it would've all been over.
'Cause I'm so kind. Just one please and it would've all been over.
Let's go.
It's a big door.
Yeah, it is.
You got this.
Okay, any day now.
I'm enough for them. I can do this for...
My beautiful friend, my one-day friend.
Beautiful friend, I will release thee!
Oh my god, you did it!
Wow! Yay!
How did I bodge it?
Yay!
Why did I bodge it?
Woo-hoo! You're free!
Yeah, let's go!
Good for you.
Uh, give me your hand, please. I need to get down from here.
Give me your hand, please. I need to get down from here.
You can't even lay yourself out. Okay.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Yeah, that's more like it, yeah.
That really put you in your place.
Okay. That was really okay. I'll let it slide because you freed me.
That was really okay. I'll let it slide because you freed me.
Yeah, that's how you show appreciation.
Well, I think we should celebrate. Celebrate!
Celebrate your freedom?
Yeah, yeah!
That's going to be so good.
We're going to like... You're going to treat me to something, right?
You're going to treat me to something, right?
I'll treat you to something afterwards.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then I'll put a good word in to your higher-ups, and it'll be wonderful.
And I'll put a good word in to your higher-ups.
I don't even have higher-ups. You keep saying I have higher-ups.
I don't even have higher-ups. You keep saying I do.
You know, you never know. Life is surprising.
You never know. Life is surprising.
Really?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm sure you also have a boss, too, right?
I'm sure you also have a boss, too, right?
Yeah!
Ouch!
When did you get so strong?
I've been training recently.
Wow!
It shows!
Oh, your hands are so big. Don't make it weird.
I didn't mean to.
人を過度に信じないように 愛さないように 期待しないように
So I won’t be trusting, and so I won’t be loving, I’ll never hope for anything
かと言って角が立たないように 気取らないように 目立たないように
Even then, I’ll go along, acting very carefully, ego never growing...
誰一人傷つけないように 虐めないように 殺さないように
So I won’t be hurting, and so I’m not a bully, I won’t give in to murdering
無駄に自我を晒さぬように 話さぬように 分からぬように
So I won’t expose me and so you’ll never know me, you won’t be getting close to me
でも絶対口を閉じさぬように 笑わすより笑われるように
Even then, I’ll go along, always speaking freely, making them laugh instead of me
人をちゃんと敬うように 崇めるように 讃えるように
Coming off politely, praising them very highly, admiring all their qualities
でも決して嫌味にならないように ぶざけないように
Never speaking bitterly, so I don't act ignorantly
ビターチョコデコレーション 兎角言わずにたんと召し上がれ
Bitter choco decoration, be sure to eat it ’till it’s gone and don’t you say a word
ビターチョコデコレーション 食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さないとね
Bitter choco decoration, a picky eater through and through, you still have much to learn
頭空っぽその後に残る心が本物なら きっと君だって同じこと
Empty out your mind and then you’ll realize, if your heart is real, surely you’re the same
「ところで一つ伺いますが 先日前何処かで…やっぱいいや」
“By the way I wanna know, if a couple days ago, did we at that time—you know what? Hey never mind.”
ビターチョコデコレーション 集団参加の終身刑
Bitter choco decoration, prison bound, we participate
またへーこらへーこら言っちゃって
Here I go, yet again, saying “what—? no way!”
「あれっ前髪ちょーぜつさいきょーじゃん!」
“I’m in awe ’cause your bangs, yeah they’re all the craze!”
とかどーでもいーのに言っちゃって
Even though, what I see, yeah, it’s all the same
毎朝毎晩もう限界 宗教的社会の集団リンチ
Morning or night, I’ll snap, you see? Misstep while they’re watching, face a group lynching
でも決して発狂しないように ビターチョコデコレーション
But it’s do or die! Survive insanity! Bitter choco decoration
ときに孤独な愛は君を汚す ビターチョコデコレーション
You know that every now and then a “love” will bring you “pain”. Bitter choco decoration
立つ鳥の後きずものアート 初めは大層な大言壮語を並べたが
They’re gonna leave you far behind, their art forever stained. Way back at the start, with dreams, I could impress
嫌よ嫌よも好きの内 「いやはややしがし今日が初めてでこんなとはね 君センスあるよ」
Now it’s tossed aside, no one cares, no one obsessed. “Hey, I gotta say that today we were amazed...”
恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション
Love in season, give a reason, bitter choco decoration
恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション F.U.C.K.Y.O.U
Love in feeling, give a meaning, bitter choco decoration, F.U.C.K.Y.O.U
望む理想に憧れて ビターチョコデコレーション
Everyone desires ideal dreams, bitter choco decoration
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さないとね 頭空っぽその後に
A picky eater through and through, empty out your mind
残る心が本物なら きっと君だって同じこと
And then you'll realize, if your heart is real, surely you're the same
主人公この就神権 まだへーこらへーこライっちゃって
The protagonist's divine right, going along and saying "whatever"
前髪調節最強じゃん ここどうでもいいのに言っちゃって
Perfect bangs, saying whatever even if it doesn't matter
迷い迷い万物限界宗教的社会の集団に決して発狂しないように
Lost and hesitating at the limit of the religious society's group, making sure not to go crazy
ビターチョコデコレーション ときに孤独ないのちを君を汚す
Bitter choco decoration, sometimes lonely life stains you
ビターチョコデコレーション テスト鳥のあときっとそのあと
Bitter choco decoration, after the test bird surely after that
初めはあなた体操さ 再会そうさ 祭典そうさ 並べたが
At first it was your gymnastics reunion, lining up...
いやよいやよも好きの内 いやはやしかし今日が初めてで こんなとはね 君センスあるよ
No, no means yes, but today is the first time... you have good sense!
恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション 恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration in the season of love
懲りすぎた季節にビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration with over-polished feelings
懲りすぎた気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration, feeling it too much
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U ビターチョコデコレーション
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U, bitter choco decoration
皆が望む理想に憧れて ビターチョコデコレーション
Longing for the ideals everyone desires, bitter choco decoration
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さないとね 頭空っぽその後に
A picky eater must be fixed properly, empty out your head after that
残る心が本物なら きっと君だって同じこと
If the heart that remains is real, surely you'll do the same
ビターチョコデコレーション 僕もあの子にやっとなったよママ
Bitter choco decoration, I finally became like that girl, Mom
明日かもきっとこの世も地獄は続くどこまでも
Tomorrow too, surely this world's hell will continue anywhere
裸からどうこう今だけは 子どもの頃の気持ちのままで
From bare to how, just for now, remaining with the feelings of a child
石集めどわずにやってこうぜ あー思い出した あったあの時の真面目そうな
Let's do it without gathering stones. Ah, I remembered that earnest-looking...
やっぱりいいや やっぱいいや
Never mind, never mind after all
Oh, thank goodness. Okay, wow, I'm free now.
So can I finally get going? Woohoo! Yeah! Woo!
Wait, what?
I just got out of here. What? What's going on? Why? Why don't you stand there, do something?
Why? Why?
Oh...
Oh, what happened?
Oh, what the heck? Where are my—where are my beautiful clothes? What?
Oh my god! My—my long, luscious hair! What happened?
I—I can't— What?
What is this? I can't even take it off!
I mean, oh god, at least I still look beautiful, but like, what happened?
Oh man, I don't know what's going on.
Oh, what is this place anyway?
しょっぱいぜ初めて嗅いで舐めた出会い
A pathetic first encounter I tasted and smelled.
自暴自棄です平均的な正論が貧乏
Self-destructive, ordinary truths feel so impoverished.
いらっしゃいませニンニク増しで目指した健康体
Welcome, aiming for a healthy body with extra garlic.
腹歌満たしてる
Filling my stomach with song.
優等生無知なフリして踊っちゃって欠点です
Playing the clueless honor student, dancing away my flaws.
現状把握しちゃって中断中もう譲って見せびらかし合い
Grasping the situation, now interrupted, showing off to each other.
劣等感も変えられないって分かってるからぁ？
Knowing I can't even change my inferiority complex, huh?
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An intuitive, self-centered, incomprehensible player.
求められてなら三時間
If requested, I'll give you three hours.
くだらん口喧嘩でマシになった
A pointless argument made things slightly better.
モットー、モットー？も意外と辛いのに
More, more? Even though it's surprisingly harsh.
うざいくらい叫んだってくれてきずれない日々を
Screaming annoyingly, shielding unbreakable days.
栄養になってまた汚し合え
Becoming nourishment, let's taint each other again.
残機わかんなくてあがんなくて脊髄反射の
With no extra lives, no energy, spinal reflexes...
涙腺は濁った声で歌えば感謝です
My tear ducts singing in a muddy voice is pure gratitude.
試したいのは暖かくて
What I want to try is warm,
絶対絶命な夜は気持ちいい
A desperate night feels so good.
平凡な生活夢見たけど
I dreamed of an ordinary life, but...
先手必勝が気持ちいいなぁ
Striking first feels so good.
帰ってすぐに水やり人間の営み
Coming home right away to water plants, human activities.
実のところ恵まれても虚無感が友達
Truth be told, even when blessed, emptiness is my friend.
眠気覚まし耳打ち飲み干すまで愛すッチ
Waking up, whispering, loving until it's drunk dry.
仲良しおよしの時間
Friendly, cozy time.
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An intuitive, self-centered, incomprehensible player.
求められてなら三時間
If requested, I'll give you three hours.
細かいご指摘も有難い
Even minor feedback is appreciated.
結局瞳孔開いてしまうのに
Even though my pupils end up dilating anyway.
うざいくらい叫んだってくれてきずれない日々を
Screaming annoyingly, shielding unbreakable days.
栄養になってまた汚し合え
Becoming nourishment, let's taint each other again.
残機わかんなくてあがんなくて脊髄反射の
With no extra lives, no energy, spinal reflexes...
涙腺は濁った声で歌えば感謝です
My tear ducts singing in a muddy voice is gratitude.
試したいのは暖かくて
What I want to try is warm,
絶対絶命な夜は気持ちいい
A desperate night feels so good.
平凡な生活夢見たけど
I dreamed of an ordinary life, but...
先手必勝が気持ちいいなぁ
Striking first feels so good.
ただ穏やかでいたい誰にも迷惑かけたくはないと思うが
I just want to be peaceful, not wanting to trouble anyone, but...
戦わないと舐めてもらえない
If I don't fight, no one will take me seriously.
単純明快でした
It was simple and clear.
うざいくらい叫んだってくれてきずれない日々を
Screaming annoyingly, shielding unbreakable days.
栄養になってまた汚し合え
Becoming nourishment, let's taint each other again.
残機わかんなくてあがんなくて脊髄反射の涙腺は濁った声で歌えば感謝です
With no extra lives, no energy, spinal reflexes singing in a muddy voice is gratitude.
言い残すことジャンケンご愛嬌じゃ
Anything left to say? Rock-paper-scissors, for charm's sake.
まずは実感湧くまで誤魔化せ
First, fake it until it feels real.
すぐ吐けなくて呆れなくて脊髄反射の涙腺は萎んだ脳で歌えば感謝です
Unable to throw up right away, not even shocked, spinal reflexes singing with a withered brain is gratitude.
試したいのはさり気ない図々しく
What I want to try is casually, brazenly,
笑えないことで笑いたかった
Laughing at things that aren't funny.
見下されないぞと変われるでも疲れると剥がれ落ちる
Not wanting to be looked down on, I can change, but when tired, it peels off.
匙にはセッション絶頂で健康で気持ちいいな
Spoonful of session, at the peak, healthy, feels so good.
あ、ちょっと君に伝えたい何かが合ったような
Ah, I want to tell you something, as if something happened.
けったい真逆の踊るベールサカサマだと知って
Knowing it's a bizarre, opposite, dancing veil turned upside down.
好意とは魅惑のプログラム
Affection is a captivating program.
ただ差し詰めここから行き着くは愛
In short, what we arrive at from here is love.
アイデンティティ
Identity.
それは思考のアイデンティティ
That is the identity of thought.
アイデンティティ呻れ君一人のせい
Identity groans, it's all because of you alone.
まだ捨てないで待ってそれは一つ二つのデスティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait, that's one or two destinies.
繋げてハッピー落ちる流れ星と歪なあの星ならあららら
Connect them, happy, falling shooting stars and that distorted star, ah la la la...
重なる面影に寄り添うそっと君に寄り添う
Nestling up to overlapping traces, gently nestling up to you.
弾け出す視界胸に飛び込むハート
A bursting field of vision, a heart leaping into my chest.
光るあなたのアイデンティティ
Your shining identity
難関プライド 飛び込めデンジャラス
Jump into difficult pride, dangerous!
さっと羽ばたく 強気の狂気と
Flapping swiftly with strong madness,
そんで裏切り お涙頂戴
and then betrayal, pulling at your tears.
ランブラララと 足取りデンジャラス
La la la, with dangerous footsteps,
背後隠れた 二人にフォーカス
focusing on the two hidden behind.
やっと見つけた 不思議の正体
Finally found the mysterious true identity.
きっと恋とは 真逆のプログラム ただ差し詰めここから行き着くは愛
Surely love is the opposite program, leading straight to love.
アイデンティティ それは希望のアイデンティティ
Identity, that's the identity of hope.
アイデンティティ 唸れ 君一人のせい
Identity, groan, it's all because of you.
まだ捨てないで待って それは一つ二つのデススティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait, it's one or two destinies.
すぐさまハッピー 落ちる 流れ星と歪なあの星
Instantly happy, falling with a shooting star and that distorted star.
重なる面影に寄り添う そっと君に寄り添う
Nestling up softly to overlapping traces, gently nestling up to you.
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込むハート
Bursting sight, a heart leaping into your chest,
刻むあなたの アイデンティティ
carving your identity.
えっとね、お花が咲いた時はすごいびっくりしたんだけど、
Um, when the flowers first bloomed, I was really surprised,
今日はすごいお誕生日の素敵な日なので、ここにこれてとっても嬉しいです。お誕生日おめでとう！
but today is a wonderful birthday, so I'm so happy to be here. Happy birthday!
あんこです。…あんこです。オンリーあんこ。
Anko. ...Anko. Only anko.
うそ、うそやけど…いっぱいあるけどあんこが一番好きです。
Just kidding, just kidding... There are a lot, but anko is my favorite.
あのね、えっと、RPGと…えっと、ローグライクのゲームが好きです。
Well, um, I like RPGs and... um, roguelike games.
アクションが苦手… ゲーマーです。
Action games are hard... I'm a gamer, though.
でも簡単なのが好きです。
But I like easy ones.
その発表のイラストなので、ちょっと派手に、なんかこう、でっかくみんなが楽しんでくれるように絵にしました。
Since it's the announcement illustration, I made it a bit flashy and big so everyone could enjoy it.
可愛く描けたと思います。
I think I drew it cute.
デザインのバッグ
design and the bag
そしてサポート、すごくクール！
and you can show your support. It'd be so cool!
うー！やったー！
Woo! Yeah!
そして、こちらの次は……じゃーん！
And then we have this next, tada!
クロニー・ラヴ！缶バッジです
It's going to be a Kronii Love! Button Badge
やったー！キラキラ、ハート型でグリッターなホログラム
and yay! Kira-kira, heart-shaped and glittery holographic—
おっと！缶バッジ！
Whoa whoa! Can badge!
ファン活動にぴったりで、次のグッズと組み合わせられるよ、こちら！
And it's going to be perfect for fan activities, and you can combine it with the next product, which is this one!
やったー！推しバッグ！やったー！
Yay! An Oshi Bag! Yay!
グッズを飾れるクリアウィンドウ付き、ぬいぐるみとか缶バッジとかね。お楽しみに！
And it comes with a clear window where you can display merch, like a plushie or the can badge. So keep that in mind! Woohoo!
そして次はこれ！
And then next we have this!
まだ見てないなら、私の衣装モチーフ、神聖なちびぬいぐるみのキーホルダー！
If you haven't seen already, it's based off of my—well, not next—my outfit, Divine Chibi Plushie Keychain!
めっちゃワクワク！やったー！
And it's going to be so exciting! Yay!
そして、フルセット購入特典もあります！やったー！
And then there's a set purchase bonus, and yay!
数量限定で、直筆サイン入りオリジナルカードと、2つ目は「レミニセンス」という特典ボイスパック！
And the limited quantity includes an original card with a handwritten signature, and the second one is a bonus voice pack called "Reminiscence."
でも安心して、売り切れても、箔押しサイン入りオリジナルカードやボイスパックがもらえるよ！
And don't worry, even when those run out, you still get other bonuses, like an original card with a foil-stamped replica signature and the voice pack!
そして改めて、全体のまとめを見たいなら、こちらがフルセット！やったー！
And yeah, once again, if you want to see the entire summary, here's the full set! Yay!
買うならフルセットが間違いなし！クロニーの誕生日はこれで全部、やったー！
And if you're going to buy, the full set is the way to go, obviously! And that's all for Ouro Kronii's birthday! Woohoo! Yay!
みんな、ぜひ買ってね！
Be sure to buy it, everyone!
そしてさらに新しいニュース！見てこれ！
And we have even more news! Take a look at this!
初のフィジカルEP「Way 2 U」が正式に決定しました！配信終了後すぐに発売開始で、アルバムには5曲収録されています、やったー！
The release of my first physical EP "Way 2 U" has been officially decided. Sales will start right away after the stream ends, and the album contains 5 tracks, yay!
収録曲は「Way 2 U」「Storm」「I'm Human 2」「Hibiscus」、そしてもちろんクラシックの「Daydream」！
And this includes "Way 2 U", "Storm", "I'm Human 2", "Hibiscus", and of course the classic "Daydream"!
CDとLPレコード盤のバージョンがあるから、比較してみてね！直筆サインポスターもつくよ！
There's a CD plus an LP vinyl version, so maybe you can compare them! It also comes with a hand-signed poster.
「Way 2 U」は3月15日にデジタルシングルとしてリリース、日本時間今夜深夜から配信スタート！見逃さないでね！
"Way 2 U" will be released as a digital single on March 15th, and distribution starts at midnight Japan time tonight, so don't miss it!
ふう、盛りだくさんだったね！この後はママと一緒に歌うよ、お楽しみに！
Whew, that was a mouthful! But after this, I'd like to sing a song together with one of my mamas, so let's enjoy this! Yay!
あーもう本当になんて
Ah, what a wonderful
素晴らしい世界
world...
んできょうもまた
And today once again,
己の醜さに惑う
I'm confused about my ugliness.
あーもう本当になんて素晴らしい世界
Ah, what a truly wonderful world...
んで今日も又己の醜さに悩む
And today, I'm once again troubled by my ugliness.
だなのに人を好きって想う気持ちだけは
Even so, the feeling of wanting to love someone
一丁前にあるから悶えてるんでしょう
is fully there, which is why I'm agonizing over it.
Ugly 正直言って
Ugly, honestly speaking,
私の顔はそう神様が左手で描いたみたい
my face is as if God drew it with His left hand.
必然この世にあるラブソングはどれひとつ
Inevitably, out of all the love songs in this world,
絶対私向けなんかじゃないでしょう
not a single one is meant for me at all.
使い道のないくちづけ 憐みを欲しいままに
Useless kisses, keeping pity all to myself,
スパンコールの棺桶で身を守る
protecting myself inside a sequined coffin.
愛されないくらいなんだ
It's just that I'm unlovable...
ギラギラ輝いて私は夜を踊り
Gira-gira, shining bright, I dance through the night,
Rap Tap Tap Tap
今に見とれろこのluv
just you wait and see this luv.
目に染みるのは1mgの花火
What stings my eyes is 1mg of fireworks,
Drag on Drag on
なんてファニー この世はビザール
How funny, this world is so bizarre.
Unknown お釈迦様も存ぜぬうちに
Unknown, before even Buddha knew,
もう健やかに狂っていたみたい
it seems I had already gone healthily crazy.
それは世界の方か それとも私の方ですか
Is that the world's doing, or is it mine?
共生は端からムリでしょう
Coexistence was out of the question from the start.
マガイモノこそかなしけれ
Imitations are all the more sorrowful,
無我夢中疾る疾る
running and running in a frantic daze.
強い酸性雨が洗い流す前に
Before the strong acid rain washes it away,
蛍光色の痣抱いて
I embrace my fluorescent bruise.
メラメラ火を吹いて私は夜の狼
Mela-mela, breathing fire, I'm a wolf of the night,
Rap Tap Tap Tap
そこで見とれろこの乱舞
watch my wild dance right there.
強くおなり あなたなりの
Be strong, in your own way,
Flap up Flap up
なんてファニー この世はビザール
how funny, this world is so bizarre.
孤独はガソリン 寂れた町を行く 目を閉じて
Loneliness is the gasoline, walking through a deserted town, closing my eyes—
もういいかい もういいかい
Are you ready yet? Are you ready yet?
もしも神様が左手利きなら どんなに幸せか知らない
If God were left-handed, I can't imagine how happy I'd be.
ギラギラ輝いて私は夜を踊り
Gira-gira, shining bright, I dance through the night,
Rap Tap Tap Tap
今に見とれろこのluv
just you wait and see this luv.
目に染みるのは1mgの花火
What stings my eyes is 1mg of fireworks,
Drag on Drag on
なんてファニー この世はビザール
how funny, this world is so bizarre.
Give love 花は満ちて
Give love, flowers are blooming,
ありのままじゃいられない 誰も 誰も
nobody can ever just stay as they are.
なんて素晴らしい世界だ ギラついていこう
What a wonderful world, let's keep on shining brightly!
“This stream depicts events for dramatization and may differ from the official canon.”
Fall in Grace Oura Keoni Birthday Live 2026
Fall in Grace - Oura Keoni Birthday Live 2026